Let's take a moment to think about what a trading algorithms goal should be.
我们来思考下交易算法的目标应该是什么
The obvious part is making money i.e,
很明显的一个目标是赚钱
we should try to generate as much positive returns from trading as possible
即尽量从交易中获得更多的回报
but the stock market is inherently very unpredictable as we have already seen.
但是我们已经知道 股市本身完全不可预测
One approach is to buy stocks that have been showing
一种策略是买入一直稳定增长的股票
consistent growth and hold onto them for long periods of time.
并长期持有它们
This usually generates some returns but nothing
通常能够产生一定的回报 但是并不可观
spectacular unless you happen to pick stocks that grow spectacularly.
除非你选择的是增长幅度很大的股票
But, how you tell ahead of time?
但是如何提前知道呢？
What if they don't do as well or even fall?
如果它们表现并不是太好 甚至很糟糕呢？
This inherent risk in the market is very real.
市场的这种固有风险是很常见的
It is as much part of the game as the actual stock prices.
实际股价本身就像一场游戏 充满不确定性
To mitigate this risk,
为了降低这种风险
you should maintain a fairly broad portfolio stocks instead of investing a handful.
你应该保持一个相当广泛的投资组合 而不是孤注一掷
How you choose these stocks can affect how much
如何选择这些股票会影响到
your returns are affected by market behavior.
市场波动对收益的影响幅度
For instance, you could buy a collection of different technology stocks,
例如 你可以买入一系列不同的科技股
so the value of your portfolio will go up.
如果这个行业总体呈增长趋势
If there's general growth across the sector,
那么你的投资组合的价值会上升
you would be somewhat immune to the chance of individual companies failing badly
某个公司业绩很差也不会影响到你
or you can bind stocks from different sectors to create a more diverse portfolio.
或者你可以买入不同行业的股票 形成更多样化的投资组合
It will be less sensitive to
任何特定行业的变化带来的影响都不会太大
any particular sector but is also not likely to go through the roof.
但是也不太可能获得巨大回报
This is because in order to generate large returns,
这是因为如果要产生大量回报
all these sectors will need to perform well together.
所有这些行业都需要表现很好
It is much more likely for only some stocks or sectors to perform strongly.
更有可能只有某些股票或行业表现强劲
Which means the average performance of all the other sectors will reduce any such effect.
所以所有其他行业的平均业绩将降低这种正面影响
So, how do you go about picking your basket of stocks?
那么如何选择股票投资组合呢？
You could perform complex statistical analysis to find collections that are likely to
你可以进行复杂的统计学分析
generate good returns but also reduce the overall risk.
寻找很可能产生高的回报并且能降低总体风险的投资组合
If you're just investing your personal money,
如果你只是投资你的个人资金
this might be too much work.
这种工作量可能太大了
Not everyone who wants to invest they have
并非每个投资者都具有相关知识和技能
the knowledge and skills to conduct a proper analysis.
来做出合理的分析
For this reason, many banks and
所以 很多银行
other financial institutions offer investment funds which are managed by professionals.
和其他金融机构会推出由专业人士管理的基金
Mutual funds are one such option which pulling money from
共同基金就是其中一种形式
multiple investors and then buy shares on their behalf.
共同基金从多个投资者那获得资金并代表他们买入股票
You can choose funds according to your investment goals.
你可以根据投资目标选择基金
Some are designed to reduce risk,
某些基金的目的是降低风险
yield a lower expected rate of return while others
预计回报率更低
are configured to give a higher rate of return at increased risk.
而其他基金的目的是产生更高的回报率 但是风险更高
Some funds track the performance of specific sectors such as infrastructure,
某些基金会关注特定行业的业绩
technology, communications, et cetera while others may be tied to specific indices.
例如基础设施 技术 通信等 而其他基金可能关注于特定的指数股票
In addition to combining multiple stocks,
除了将多支股票组合到一起之外
some funds are traded on stock exchanges themselves.
有些基金本身也在证交所交易
That is, in order to invest money in these funds,
也就是说 想要投资这些基金
you buy their shares on the market.
你需要买入它们的股票
Hence, they are known as Exchange Traded Funds or ETFs.
所以它们称之为交易所交易基金 (ETF)
They are very popular investments for stock market investors as it tend to produce
它们在股市上是很热门的投资产品
some growth as long as the sector or index they're tracking does well.
因为只要它们关注的行业或指数表现不错 它们就有增长
In addition to mitigating risk,
除了降低风险之外
they are also much more economically compared to investing in many stocks individually,
与投资多个单独的股票相比 它们更经济
because you typically have to pay
因为通常每支股票
brokerage and other transaction fees on them separately.
都需要支付经纪费和其他交易费用
A popular ETF is Standard &amp; Poor's 500 or
热门的 ETF 包括标准普尔 500指数 (S&amp;P 500)
S&amp;P 500 which trades under the ticker symbol SPY.
它的股票代码是 SPY
The S&amp;P 500 include 500 stocks with
S&amp;P 500 包括 500 支
the large market capitalization that trade on the New York Stock Exchange or Nasdaq,
在纽约证交所或纳斯达克上市的大型市值股票
selected from diverse sectors.
它们来自于不同的行业
The composition of an ETF,
ETF 的股票和比例构成
the stocks and their proportions can vary over time.
随着时间的推移会变化
This gives rise to another source of
这样就会带来另一个
information that can be useful in making trading decisions.
在做出交易决策时有用的信息来源
ETF compositional data.
即 ETF 成分股数据
For example, let's say you want to diversify your investment to reduce market risk.
例如 假设你想多样化你的投资 从而降低市场风险
You do that by analyzing the individual performance or correlations between stocks.
分析个股业绩或者不同股票的相关性
This generates a portfolio that is well-balanced and not too correlated.
能够得出一个平衡性很好 但是关系并不太紧密的投资组合
If you include ETFs like SPY in your portfolio,
如果你在投资组合中添加了 SPY 等 ETF
then there will be some correlation between
那么 ETF 和所包含的
the ETFs and the individual company stocks that they are made up of.
单个企业股票之间就存在一定的相关性
Now, instead of trying to compute these correlations from historic data,
如果你能查看所含股票的精确比例
wouldn't it be better if you had access to the exact proportion of stocks used.
而不用通过历史数据计算这些关系 是不是更好？
That's precisely what an ETF compositional data provides.
ETF 成分数据就能提供这种信息
Using this information, you can obtain a much more accurate measure of how correlated
利用这些信息 你能够更准确地衡量
the stocks in a portfolio are and balance them out to further mitigate risks.
投资组合中的股票之间的相关性 并平衡它们以进一步降低风险